hdnicewallpapers.com 2019-06-09

# Privacy Policy | HD Nice Wallpapers

Thank you for visiting hdnicewallpapers.com takes your online privacy seriously. This document outlines the types of information collected by our servers and provides links to the privacy policies of our third-party advertising partners. Please read the following to learn more about how we protect and respect your personal privacy.

User Accounts

No user account is required in order to browse or download the content we provide. To better protect your privacy, the following notice explains our online information practices and the choices you can make about the collection and use of the personal information you submit on web pages where this Privacy Policy is posted. 

Personally Identified Data

We strongly discourage users from entering their full name, city, email, or other sensitive information in user profiles, comments, contacts, or other areas of the site. Furthermore, we request that minors and any individuals with limited decision making ability not create an account on this site without the approval and supervision of a guardian. 

We make a reasonable attempt to monitor for cases where users post personally identifiable information about other individuals to public portions of the web site and remove the offending material.

Server Logs

Like most web sites, hdnicewallpapers.com logs web, database, and other server-software usage and access information. This information may include your internet protocol (IP) address, which in many cases can be translated to an affiliation (such as your work, school, or internet service provider), or a geographical location. We only use this information for debugging purposes and for aggregating into anonymous usage and traffic statistics.

Cookies

This Website uses cookies. A cookie is a small, removable data file that is stored by your web browser on your computer. Cookies allow you to place an order on this Website and allow us to enhance, facilitate and personalize your online surfing and shopping experience. For example, we use cookies to : 

  1. Recognize you when you return to this Website.
  2. Remember your stored preferences on this Website.
  3. Present relevant content to you when you visit this Website.
  4. Analyze visitor behavior.
  5. Facilitate other similar type of activities.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your web browser settings. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your visit to this Website more efficient and enjoyable, and in some cases, some of our services will not function or will function with limited capability.

Sharing/Selling of Data

hdnicewallpapers.com does not share or sell personally identifiable data to third parties such as spammers or direct marketers. We respect your privacy.

Third-Party Advertisers

hdnicewallpapers.com serves ads provided by a range of third-party advertising networks. The practices of our advertising partners are not directly covered by hdnicewallpapers.com's privacy policy. We recommend that you read their policies. For your convenience we provide a list our advertising partners below. Unfortunately we cannot guarantee it is always comprehensive and up to date. - [Google AdSense](https://www.google.com/adsense/)

External Links

Our site may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by organizations sponsoring these other sites.

Other Websites

When browsing this Website, you may be directed to other websites that are beyond our control. These other websites may use cookies and pixel tags, collect data, or solicit personal information. Even though hdnicewallpapers.com may be affiliated with these websites, we have no control over them or how they collect, distribute or otherwise use your personal information or how they safeguard and secure your personal information. hdnicewallpapers.com is not responsible or liable for the conduct, policies or actions of the owners of such websites or the content displayed on these websites. These websites are linked to this Website only for your convenience and you access them at your own risk.

Children's Online Privacy

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 18\. This Website is not intended to solicit information of any kind from children under the age of 18 and we have made commercially reasonable efforts to design this Website to prevent our knowing acceptance of any such information. It is possible that by fraud, deception or error, we may receive information pertaining to children under the age of 18. If we are notified of this, as soon as we verify the information, we will immediately obtain parental consent or otherwise delete the information from our servers. If you want to notify us of our receipt of personal information belonging to a child under the age of 18, please don't forget to Contact Us.

Questions and Feedback

We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about this Privacy Policy and our privacy practices. Please send us feedback pertaining to these matters or any other issue you may have with hdnicewallpapers.com or this Website. You may contact us using the contact form located at www.hdnicewallpapers.com/Contacts.

Data Retention

The data submitted to and generated by this web site may be copied to additional machines for redundancy and backup purposes. 

If you have still any problems or questions don't forget to Contact Us.
